Hello, everyone.
Cześć wszystkim.
I'm so glad that you are here.
Tak się cieszę, że tu jesteś.
Welcome to my course, complete Linux training course to get your dream it job.
Witaj na moim kursie, ukończ kurs szkoleniowy Linux, aby zdobyć wymarzoną pracę.
Now, let me put it in a very simple way.
Teraz pozwólcie, że przedstawię to w bardzo prosty sposób.
When you take this course, you will learn so many things about Linux that you're going to be able to
Kiedy weźmiesz udział w tym kursie, nauczysz się tak wielu rzeczy o Linuksie, że będziesz mógł ubiegać
apply for a Linux job and you will get the job.
się o pracę w Linuksie i ją zdobędziesz.
Fair enough.
Słusznie.
My name is Imran Afsal and I've been in it specifically in Linux field for more than two decades now.
Nazywam się Imran Afsal i od ponad dwóch dekad zajmuję się tym szczególnie w dziedzinie Linuksa.
I have actually worked in New York City for fashion industry, for tech media firms, for financial
Właściwie pracowałem w Nowym Jorku dla branży modowej, firm zajmujących się mediami technologicznymi, firm finansowych,
firms, for cloud and hosting companies, you name it.
firm zajmujących się chmurą i hostingiem.
I did complete my bachelors in Computer Information Systems from Baruch College, City University of
Ukończyłem licencjat z Computer Information Systems na Baruch College, City University of New York oraz
New York and my MBA from New York Institute of Technology.
tytuł MBA na New York Institute of Technology.
I teach in a very simple language, and I don't assume that you know a little bit more about Linux.
Uczę w bardzo prostym języku i nie zakładam, że wiesz trochę więcej o Linuksie.
I will actually hold your hand every step of the way throughout this course, and I will make sure you
Będę trzymał cię za rękę na każdym kroku podczas tego kursu i upewnię się,
understand everything.
że wszystko rozumiesz.
There are so many of my students here on Udemy who actually took this course and they were able to pass
Na Udemy jest tak wielu moich studentów, którzy faktycznie wzięli udział w tym kursie i
any of the Linux certification and they were able to get the job of their dreams.
byli w stanie zdać dowolny certyfikat z Linuksa i mogli dostać pracę swoich marzeń.
So what are you waiting for?
Więc na co czekasz?
Let's go ahead and enroll.
Chodźmy i zarejestruj się.